warwick.ac.uk 2006-11-02

# Web site terms and conditions, University of Warwick

#### 1\. Copyright

All rights, including copyright, in the content of these web pages (including, but not limited to, the University logo, and all text, layout, graphics, icons and artwork) are owned or controlled for these purposes by the University of Warwick unless otherwise stated.

Content on web pages at Warwick is the responsibility of the page owner and does not necessarily represent the views of the University of Warwick.

Warwick's web pages contain links to many external web sites which are not affiliated with the University of Warwick.  The University is not responsible for and has no control over these sites, and links to external sites should not be taken as a recommendation or endorsement of the external site's information, products or services.

In accessing the university's web pages, you agree that you may only download the content for your own personal non-commercial use.  The material on these web pages should not be used, copied, stored or transmitted outside the University without the prior written consent of the University or in accordance with the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988.

#### 2\. Privacy

The University of Warwick recognises that personal privacy is an important issue, and we support the protection of internet privacy as required by UK legislation.

This statement explains what types of personal information will be gathered when you visit the University of Warwick's web site and how this information will be used. Please note that although Warwick's web site provides links to other web sites, this policy only applies to the University's web pages (ie. those ending in warwick.ac.uk).

Personal information is neither captured nor stored through the Warwick web site without the prior consent of users. Where personal information is captured (eg. through web forms for feedback, requests, etc.), the user will be informed as to what information is being captured and why. Any personal information that you provide to us will be used only for the purpose stated at the time we request it. We will not sell, license or trade your personal information to others. We do not provide your personal information to direct marketing companies or other such organisations.

In addition, some parts of the Warwick web site require authentication with a username and/or password. These pages use cookies for security purposes. These cookies are not used to capture or store personal information for any purpose other than to authenticate the user, and are deleted as soon as a session is terminated. Information about the pages visited by logged-in users is stored for statistical analysis purposes, but individual usage patterns are not monitored.

It is also possible to make credit card payments to the University of Warwick through our web site. Such payments are handled by a third party e-commerce company called WorldPay, and they have their own [privacy statement](http://www.worldpay.com/about_us/index.php?page=privacy).

Finally, the Warwick web site maintains logs of its servers' activity. These log files include the IP address of every computer used to access the Warwick web site. The log files are used to analyse usage of the Warwick web site.

It is also important to point out that in certain circumstances the University may be obliged to disclose information or undertake more detailed monitoring under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000. A page with more detailed information on this topic may be found [here](http://www2.warwick.ac.uk/services/its/helpfaq/policies/ripa/ "Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 at the University of Warwick").

If you use web applications at Warwick other than as a reader, then some additional information about your activities may be stored.  This list of Warwick web applications explains what additional data is stored for each application:-
